And the same thing works for screenshots as well.
So tap the Function key again and dictate whatever
you want to dictate.
And along with the dictation you can grab screenshots.
You can navigate across different screens and grab
screenshots like you would, in a Mac.
Maybe you can copy links as well.
And once you are done gathering all the context
along with your dictation, go back to Apple Notes or any,
input box for that matter.
maybe try Apple Notes for now and tap the
Function key again to submit the whole thing finally.
And what you'll see is that it pastes your
dictation along with the things that you might have copied,
like the links or some texts.
And it also attaches all the screenshots, multiple of them,
in the same dictation attempt.
So this makes the entire input gathering process really easy for you.
It's as if you are thinking
and in the same flow you are capturing the context
so that you can send all of it as a, input to AI,
agent like ChatGPT or maybe Claude or Codex.